[{
  "front": "budu rozsvěcet",
  "back": "i will turn on"
}, {
  "front": "budu si mýt",
  "back": "i will wash"
}, {
  "front": "budu se česat",
  "back": "i will brush"
}, {
  "front": "budu zavírat",
  "back": "i will close"
}, {
  "front": "budu se vracet",
  "back": "i will return to"
}, {
  "front": "bude spát",
  "back": "i will sleep"
}, {
  "front": "budu ho budit",
  "back": "i will wake"
}, {
  "front": "budu otevírat",
  "back": "i will open"
}, {
  "front": "budu větrat",
  "back": "i will aerate"
}, {
  "front": "budu odcházet",
  "back": "i will leave"
}, {
  "front": "bude tma",
  "back": "it will be dark"
}, {
  "front": "budu filtrovat",
  "back": "i will filter"
}, {
  "front": "budu zapínat",
  "back": "will turns"
}, {
  "front": "budu otevírat",
  "back": "i will open"
}, {
  "front": "budu vybírat",
  "back": "i will pick"
}, {
  "front": "budu dávat",
  "back": "i will give"
}, {
  "front": "voda se bude vařit",
  "back": "water will boil"
}, {
  "front": "bude hotový",
  "back": "i will be ready"
}, {
  "front": "budu odcházet",
  "back": "i will leave"
}, {
  "front": "budeme mít",
  "back": "we will have"
}, {
  "front": "budu otevírat",
  "back": "i will open"
}, {
  "front": "budu přemýšlet",
  "back": "i will think about it"
}, {
  "front": "budu mít chuť",
  "back": "i will have taste"
}, {
  "front": "budu brát",
  "back": "i will take"
}, {
  "front": "budu nést",
  "back": "i will be"
}, {
  "front": "budu otevírat",
  "back": "i will open"
}, {
  "front": "budu hledat",
  "back": "i will search"
}, {
  "front": "budu nacházet",
  "back": "i will find"
}, {
  "front": "budu pokládat",
  "back": "i will treasure"
}, {
  "front": "budu krájet",
  "back": "i will slice"
}, {
  "front": "budu mazat",
  "back": "i will delete"
}, {
  "front": "budu solit",
  "back": "i will salt"
}, {
  "front": "budu vařit",
  "back": "i will cook"
}, {
  "front": "budu hledat",
  "back": "i will search"
}, {
  "front": "budu nalévat",
  "back": "i will pours"
}, {
  "front": "budu zapínat",
  "back": "i will switch on"
}, {
  "front": "se budou vařit",
  "back": "it will be cooked"
}, {
  "front": "budu čekat",
  "back": "i will wait"
}, {
  "front": "budu připravovat",
  "back": "i will prepare"
}, {
  "front": "budu mýt",
  "back": "i will wash"
}, {
  "front": "budu krájet",
  "back": "i will slice"
}, {
  "front": "budu dávat",
  "back": "i will give"
}, {
  "front": "budu volat",
  "back": "i will call"
}]